Thank you for watching!
Thank you very much.
Are you ready?
Of course I am.
Are you full of energy?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Come on.
Oh!
Hello.
Good evening.
Nice to meet you.
This week's Jessie Kushner show is about Balikata.
Balikata!
Big, big movements!
And with that, I'd like to start today's show.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
First of all, what's this?
It's like a first greeting.
Do you want to do it again?
Yes, that's right.
Yes, please.
So... how are you doing? You're doing great.
Yes, it's really good.
The Dester car is beautiful, isn't it?
It's a big car, isn't it?
Today is Friday, the 23rd of June, and tomorrow is Saturday, the 24th of June, which is the weekend.
I know some of you might be going somewhere, but I'll tell you what I'm going to do, I'm going to pull out my ufo's and fly over the flying saucer memorial day.
flying saucer anniversary.
Have you ever seen a ufo?
No, I haven't either. I didn't mean to imply that you have.
If there was, I'd be on Yaejo's show.
By the way, on this day in 1947, June 24th, a mysterious flying object like a coffee plate was seen for the first time in the U.S.A.
That was the so-called "flying saucer," or what we now call a "ufo.
Mr. Arnold, who is an American, said he saw such a flying saucer.
Mr. Arnold, who is from America, said he saw it, and then there were reports of sightings all over the U.S.
So the U.S. Air Force investigated it to see if it was really a ufo.
In 1969, an investigation reported that the ufo might have misjudged the searchlight of a car.
But later in 1969, an investigation reported that the ufo might have misjudged a car's searchlight.
I have seen it sometimes when I was driving at night and I saw a person who was fogged up and I thought he/she was looking at a cloud.
I sometimes drive at night, and when I see someone in the clouds, and a searchlight from a store shines on them from below...
I thought it was a ufo when I was a little kid.
I had a dream like that when I was a little kid in 1947
When I saw the searchlight, I thought it was a ufo.
I wish there would be a disk, you know... and the "fore" would be the same... and it would be worse...
Cows, right? Cows!
That's the universe, isn't it?
And then an octopus-like person appears... and that's the alien... and the other ones have a human shape... and you don't know what they look like...
I don't know... it doesn't matter... it's just... it'll ruin the romance of space for me!
I want people to come!
I wish people would come, I wish people would stay, I wish people would stay, I wish people would stay, I wish people would stay, I wish people would stay.
But...
But it's the anniversary of the ufo.
I have a cow. I'll be back in a little bit.
I'll be back in a little bit...
I like this one.
I'm not sure if there's such a thing as hot springs now, but we go there in the summer too.
I'm just a little bit of a hot springs expert, but I'd like to introduce Hidemi from Asaka City, Saitama Prefecture.
Genius master handsome Sawa Pon cute beauty chubby and chan comandibile ever see
This time, I went to a hot spring hotel in Tochigi during the Golden Week holidays.
I heard it's quite famous and it's located deep in the mountains with no cell phone reception and is also a famous ryokan as a filming location for "El Maero Mae.
I've always wanted to visit there, and my wish came true! Anyway, the mask of a tengu is a cat!
Anyway... this is the famous photo of the Tengu masked cat... but it's good that there's no signal.
Digital detox. That's all I've said today.
I've said that four times today...
I'm taking pictures digitally, it's like going camping and taking pictures at Disney.......
So here it is...
8, right?
a. Same reactor... Tengu...
a Tengu is also great, but this one has a really nice decoration.
Why the Tengu?
I have a scary image of a tengu... but... a tengu has a long nose... and a red face...
originally from the middle east, like Iran, they practiced Buddhism in those days, you know like a mountain festival
There were some people who came to Japan from China through that region, and they practiced Buddhism deep in the mountains.
Then, you know, they had never seen a foreigner before, and the flowers were so tall, they were so surprised, and their faces were so red.
When they saw that, they thought he was a Tengu.
And he's practicing yama-bushi (mountain dance), so he's always shouting "hooaaaaaaa!
That's the origin of the foreigner theory.
That's how it started.
And... this one's nice, too.
A fatherly man sent us a nice photo of a 50th grader from Suzuka City, Mie Prefecture.
Well, the 5-year rule is good... but it says I'll take it if I can.
I'm 62 years old.
You know, your occupation... the Ebiqi family.
I'm sure you don't know who they are... but I'm sure you think they're your grandchildren.
Oh, ah...
I'm talking about the master's regulars, Mr. Raiya, who is a member of the Ebichu family.
I took two shots with a cat on the beach that I've recently become friends with...
Master.
Thank you very much.
Wow, he's so smitten. He must've taken a selfie.
It's so relaxing... something about the shirt...
Boo Boo, you're so cute!
Wow, cats are nice. Summer is nice.
This is a nice cat.
I don't think people usually take selfies.
People who have never taken a selfie before tend to take a lot of pictures in a frame like this.
I understand that you don't feel natural at all.It's just on the other side of Tokyo. The shape of the mountains is very interesting.
I think there was a ropeway or something like that, but they sent it to me.
Yes, it's nice, isn't it?
I'll take that Kaneko Yokohashi... the illustrator...
Good evening, Master Sarpon!
I've been to the Sawtooth Mountains over the weekend, so I thought I'd send you some photos.
It's a 40 minute ferry ride from Kurihama in Kanagawa Prefecture to Kanaya Park in Chiba Prefecture, and then you can walk there.
It's not the kind of place where you can go for hours, but it's right next to the sea.
There is a statue of the Great Buddha on Sawtooth Mountain, and Kaneko, who is worshipping him, is standing in front of the statue.
I'm so glad you sent me this wonderful photo. I didn't know there was such a place in Japan.
So, in those days, people used to cut stones from here, and they used to cut them on boats.
So, they used to cut stones from here and bring them by boat, like in the Edo period, and arrange them for buildings and so on.
Back in the Edo period, I think it was the same.
Inside, there's a big statue of Buddha like this, which I think was probably dug out of the ground.
It's like Indiana Jones, isn't it? I'd love to go there.
Sawtooth Mountain It's quite high, isn't it?
It's about the size of a man. It's huge.
I love it.
I love it! There are so many mountains in Japan.
I first heard of Mt. Nokogiri not as a tourist attraction.
It was during the boom of the "driver's boom", you know, the 86 and so on.
There was a boom of driving on the mountain passes with those cars.
People drove 86s and Langebos and that kind of thing.
And on weekends, we'd gather on the good mountain passes.
There was a great road in Nokogiri Mountain back then.
I don't think they do that anymore.
I heard about it from a fellow runner.
So I went there too... no, no, no, no...
It was so far away. We didn't take the ferry.
I was like, "Wow, you haven't been there yet?
I miss the 86.
The 86 is a great car. It's a classic.
Yes, well, well, well...
That's why I'm here.
By the way... the Barrigato was born, wasn't it?
That's right, it was born
You see, it's 365 days a year
There are 365 days in a year.
There are birthdays, right?
Yes...
By the way, what day were you born on?
May 28th.
What? Huh? Huh? What?
September 29
May 29.
I don't know why I crossed it out.
I don't know why we crossed.
On the 29th.
Yes.
And you're 16?
Yes, I'm 16.
You made it. Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
Lesson's up!
That's good. It means you've turned 16.
Does turning 16 change your mind?
I don't feel it yet. I feel like 14 or something.
Now?
Slightly down, right?
I haven't changed that much since I was 14.
I turned 15 and turned 16 without really feeling it.
But from a Balinese point of view...
From our point of view, joining Shrimp Club is a turning point in your life.
It was a turning point in your life.
It's been a year since then?
Eight months.
It hasn't been a year yet.
I see... I see... How's it going?
I'm doing a lot of things with the older members now.
Are you sometimes influenced by them?
Yes, I'm influenced by them. The most influential thing is...
My tastes in food are becoming more and more mature.
That's true. The food we eat at different places...
I was the same way, but as I grew up, I've never eaten anything before.
I've never eaten anything like that before. I was like, "What's this?
But when you try it, it's delicious.
That's true, isn't it?
I do. By the way, I'm going to ask Mr. Barrie about it later.
I have the most obvious one... red pickled ginger.
I hated it when I was a kid.
You see it on yakisoba noodle stalls?
Instead of it, put bean sprouts and three noodles.
I really hated it.
But then one day, as an adult, I had a chance to try it.
I ate some red pickled ginger, and I thought, "Wow! I thought, "Wow!
If there was red ginger all at once, I'd be like...
When you come to a beef bowl restaurant, it's like this
I'm still going to eat it, aren't I?
I love it!
Salmon?
I don't know.
I used to hate mushrooms, but now I can eat them.
And avocados.
I used to hate avocados, too.
I never ate avocados when I was younger.
When I was young, there might not have been an avocado era.
I'm sure there were avocados in supermarkets.
I'm sure they existed in supermarkets in other countries.
Avocados were considered a fashionable vegetable.
And colored bell peppers.
Aren't they delicious?Aren't they delicious?
I never saw colored peppers when I was younger.
It's a recent thing.
We didn't have colored peppers in the past.
Green peppers used to be the only color.
We don't go to fancy supermarkets.
We have to go to a fancy supermarket.
Yes, yes, yes.
Some kind of Ishii-like place
We're almost out of here.
If we add some more stuff, we'll be out of here.
Ishii-san's, right?
I have to go there.
How about Barrigata?
I ate a lot of things.
I thought you've grown up.
For example, when you eat food...
Taste-wise.
I can now drink green tea and matcha, for example.
And more than anything else, the older sister members and the principal
I'd like to have something to snack on with my drinks.
as a snack.
Something like that.
I don't drink alcohol.
But I've come to like the snacks.
Appetizers.
I don't know what it was when I was a kid.
I don't know... my grandpa or something.
He's not my grandpa.
I don't know if he was my dad or my grandma.
What's this here?
Salted fish.
When I first tasted it, I thought, "Ugh!
It had a strong taste.
I thought, "What the hell is this?
But now I can't win without salted fish.
It's a must.
Then it's going to get better and better.
From now on, your taste buds will expand more and more, and you'll grow up.
I'm going to grow up.
I don't know what I want to try yet, but...
Iburi school.
Oh, that...
In Akita.
That smoked pickled radish.
It's delicious!
Cream cheese!
Yay!
Destasher.
That's a destasher.
It's a destasher.
It's the real deal.
I was so surprised the first time I had it.
It's the best.
I knew they made a special kind of takuan (pickled radish), but...
But when I went there, the cheese was on top like this.
It was like, "What's the cheese on top?
When I ate it, what was it?
I don't know why the cheese and the pickled ginger go together so well.
I don't know why cheese and Iburi gakko go so well together.
Put it on crackers.
I'll put it on crackers.
How much more Kahogo can you get?
They love him so much!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
I've never had aburi goko.
I haven't had it yet.
But I'm sure you have.
I think I'm tired of ebichu.
You do a lot of things with it.
I've never had it because I haven't had the courage to try it yet.
I've never had the courage to try it.
It's a little too hard for me.
It's true that the dipping sauce...
It's very matured.
It's a little bit ooey-gooey, isn't it?
From a kid's point of view.
I used to really dislike tsukemono, too.
I didn't like it.
Like takuan (pickled radish).
And the takuan my mom would buy for me.
They have a strange character.
You know, the yellow ones that melt out?
Artificial.
Yes, there are.
We didn't have to in our time.
I thought it was too old for that kind of thing.
But then... the "Balicata" was born.
16 years
16 years, that's a lot!
One moment, please.
Oh?
What would you like to see?
A cake.
What cake?
Shortcake, right?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
What's this?
It's from the show.
Do you know what this is?Do you know this?
BURNING NEW YORK
Burning New York is
is a very fashionable
It's very fashionable.
They sell Tiffany's and stuff like that.
High-end.
What do you call it?
A store?
Boutique.
What?
Boutique?
Boutique!
There's a boutique?
Boutique.
You know, for girls you like.
Rings.
I mean...
You go to Bernie's New York to buy a ring when you're in the right mood.
They won't even let you lowlifes in.
I've never been in there, by the way. I've seen it from the outside.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God, here you go.
What is it? You bought a ring? Thank you. Congratulations.
Please, go ahead, take a look. Well, it's not all rings and rings.
Oh, my God, isn't this amazing?
I'll open it.
What?
What's this tissue? They're very expensive.
How do we open it? Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Open it! What what what? It's like a drum.
Like sashimi drumsticks. Surely, if there were sashimi here, you'd be the one to open it.
It's funny that you're giving away sashimi balls.
Let's have a look. There's something inside.
What is it?
What's this?
Tableware? It looks like a UFO.
It's a UFO weapon.
There's another UFO.
Okay, let's see, let's see. Open it up.
It's wrapped up pretty tightly, but that means it's probably some kind of dishware.
It's bubble wrap, bubble wrap, bubble wrap, like this.
Here's some more.
What is it? A plate?
Oh?
Oh, that's it. That's it.
Coffee or tea cups.
Teacups.
Teacups and stuff.
Wow, that's cool.
It's cute.
That's so cute.
That's nice.
Oh, no. Sneaky.
Barneys, Junio's ward.
One more thing. Oh, my God, I didn't know.
It's black.
I didn't know it was black.
It's like Bernie's.
This one...
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
what is it?
Whoa, whoa, whoa
what is this?
eh, soil
Oh!
It smells good.
Well, I'll just have a cup of tea with it, then, shall I?
Wow, nice!
There's a samoar, right?
Samoa.
That coffee shop.
Wow!
It smells so good!
Amazing!
Omelette with rice!
Mulligato-chan!
From a member of Ebichu
Milk Tea
Since we're here...
Here's some milk tea too!
One shot!
What the hell!
It's like he's talking about how good it is.
What's that?
The three of us.
Samboile's.
Milk tea?
No, no, no, no, no!
What is it?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no. Thank you.
Wow!
Happy 16th!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!Yeah!
It's soooo good!
It's so good!
Oh, my God!
Royal milk.
Yes!
It's delicious, it's delicious, it's delicious, it's a little bit different than your regular love, but it tastes like a rich, high quality, real black tea, and it's got a little bit of a kick to it, too.
Yes, we have the Kitterrut.
I'm sure there are a lot of you out there who would like to congratulate us on our newest addition to our family of teas.
And the Debel Charge is here, thank you, Rain 3 Balicata, Happy Birthday, and Kashihige, Balicata.
Happy Birthday to the 3 Balikatas!
No, no, no, no, no!
That's a bit sudden, isn't it?
Boo-hoo! I really thought I'd been beaten to a pulp...
Happy birthday to Ei-chan's balicata!
Congratulations to Momoshiki-san and congratulations to Takumi-san on his balicata birthday!
Thank you very much and Mr. Crunchy, yes, Mr. Crunchy, just a little bit, it disappeared in a moment
I disappeared for a moment...
I'm so sorry, I can't see you anymore...
I'm so glad you're here!
Thank you very much! And Mr. Wantan, I don't know what he is, but he's so nice!
Thank you very much for your kindness and congratulations!
I'm sure you've heard this a lot, but I'm turning 16, and from now on I'm going to be a little haughty and haughty.
I'm sure you've been asked a lot, but I'm turning 16 and I'm going to be a Hauffe Hauffe.
I was already saying hauf, but I'm going to say hauf, hauf, hauf, hauf, hauf, hauf, hauf, hauf, hauf, hauf, hauf, hauf, hauf, hauf, hauf.
I'll do my best for a healthy year.
Why is a character becoming a character?
Yes, it's important... so congratulations!
Happy birthday to Mr. Perky and Mr. Bertie, too!
Well, well, well, well... and for those of you watching the live broadcast... thank you very much for celebrating with us today.
See you next week for the live broadcast.
And finally, for those of you watching the live broadcast... the Barry guy, right?
Yes, that's right.
It was Barry.
That's so cute. What was that?
What was that? Every time we do this, we come up with more and more variations.
Thank you very much.
Awww!
undefined